-=THE LAST FANTASY=-
-=THE LAST FANTASY=- Proudly Presents
荣誉出品
本字幕仅供学习交流 严禁用于商业途径
-=TLF字幕组=-
翻译：kobewen1
校对：DeadZombie
怎么这么早天就亮了？
How's it morning already?
杰里德
Jarrod...
杰里德 醒醒
Jarrod, wake up.
没事吧
It's okay.
那是什么？
What is that?
我不知道
I do not know.
雷！
Ray!
待这别动
Stay here.
发生什么事？
What's wrong?
他消失了！
He is gone!
杰里德！
Jarrod!
片名：《天际》
15小时之前
难以决定啊
I can't decide.
艾琳 你来挑最后一张吧
Elaine, you pick the last one.
杰里德爱摇滚 特里爱钱？
Jay-rock... T-money?
我们当时过得很糟糕 非常差劲
Well, we do had a bad time, we were bad.
你一点都没变
You haven't changed a bit.
特里也是
Neither is Terry...
等着瞧哈
You'll see.
- 他现在可是成功人士 - 我已经迫不及待了
- He is a real deal. - Can't wait.
你在说一大堆废话前就应该考虑清楚
Well you should have thought about that before you shout a piece of shit.
你这么早来这干嘛？
What are you doing here so early?
- 今天天气不错 - 我知道
- It's a beautiful day. - Well I know it.
他们打电话过来问机器人的场景 但是…
They gonna call about the robotic but...
叫他们处理吧
Tell 'em to handle it...
我生日的时候可不想事务缠身
No business on my birthday.
- 嗨 - 天啊 她怎么一直在这儿？
- Hi. - God. She always have to be here?
这是她的工作
She is working.
这就是演艺圈 亲爱的
Showbiz, baby.
你身上好多汗
You're sweatie...
- 艾琳 你还好吧？ - 恩
- Elaine, are you feeling alright? - Yeah.
是的 没事
Yeah, I'm fine...
等下 我来帮你吧
Here, let me get that for you.
给你
Here you go.
- 谢谢 - 不客气
- Thank you. - No problem.
真是我的大英雄
That's you my hero.
爱摇滚的杰里德
这是接我们的
Yeah, that's us.
噢 你是在开玩笑吧！
Oh, you got to be kidding me!
- 你可别习惯这样娇生惯养 - 说谁？我吗？
- You better not get use to this. - Who? Me?
顶层到了
Penthouse.
好的 走吧
Alright, come on.
除我以外最有才的哥们现在过得如何？
How is the second most talented guy I know?
不知道 你呢？
I don't know. How are you?
非常不错
I'm good.
生日快乐！
Happy Birthday!
噢 你一定是艾琳
Oh, You must be Elaine.
- 上帝啊 - 欢迎你
- God. - Welcome.
真是太不可思议了
This is amazing.
我的生活全部自动化
Automatic living at its finest.
我的个人公寓像是嵌在云里
My personal place in clouds.
这里的景色太美了
The view is incredible.
艾琳 我问你一下
Elaine, let me ask you a question.
你是怎么追到我哥们的？
How do you keep my boy Elaine?
别回答
Don't answer that.
这可是个艰巨的任务
It is a full-time job.
他当初给你多少钱 我双倍
Well, what ever he is paying you, I'll double it.
噢 但现在你都有两个女的了
Oh well! Its like coaching is full already.
我喜欢
I like it, yeah.
你们的房间在那
That's your room right there.
你要去泳池吗？
You guys want it to the pool?
当然
Absolutely.
亲爱的！
Baby!
戏水时间！
Pool time!
- 亲爱的 给我一杯科斯莫（鸡尾酒） - 好的 拿着
- Baby, get me a Cosmo. - Absolutely, hold this.
嘿 酒吧在这边
Hey, the bar is this way.
哥们 你真的做到了
You really did it man.
我是说 每个人现在都认识你 但是…
I mean, just like everybody knew you would but...
嗨 伙计
Hi guys!
你好…
Hello...
没有你 我什么都做不成
I kind of not done it without you.
我做了什么？帮你刷墙吗？
What I do? Decorated the walls?
- 你看起来不错哦 - 她们看起来也不错
- You do look nice. - They do look nice.
生日快乐 特里
Happy Birthday, Terry.
是的 祝我生日快乐！
Yeah, happy birthday to me!
我不能住在那 哥们
I can't live in that place man.
我都不知道拿什么礼物给你
And I don't know what I should be gettng as your gift.
我突然有些想法
I got some ideas on that.
跟我来
Come on.
我觉得你们相处得很不错哦
I see everyone getting along famously.
- 亲爱的 - 恩
- Baby! - Yeah.
我的科斯莫呢？
Where is my cosmo?
噢 我错了
Oh my bad.
丹尼斯 给我一杯饮料
Denise, get me a drink.
- 谁还要吗？ - 不要了
- Anyone else? - No.
嘿 这里可比12月份的布鲁克林区强多了
Hey, this definitely beats Brooklyn in December.
我不知道 我还是比较喜欢四季分明
I don't know... I kinda like having four seasons.
过几条街区就有了
You got one group down block.
明天我们一起出海游玩去
Tomorrow we gonna hit the high sea
驾着我的“逐日号”
and we take it hell out of my sun seeker.
67英尺长 我的入门级游艇
67 footer, my starter yacht
国安局都来了 连他们都知道
Homeland security...They must be here because they know
今晚我们的聚会会相当火爆
that our party tonight gonna be the bomb!
干杯！
Cheers.
生日快乐 特里！
Happy Birthday, Terry!
- 嗨 朋友 最近怎么样？ - 挺好的
- Hi mate, how is it going man? - Alright.
我要介绍一个人给你认识 雷！
There is somebody I want you to meet. Ray!
等下
Hold on.
生日快乐 哥们
Happy birthday man.
谢谢
Thank You.
那个“机器人战斗”的场景做得怎么样了？
How is "The Robot Fight" coming along?
糟透了！但是导演喜欢 所以…
Dude its sucks! But the director loves it, so... you know!
- 嘿 这就是那个神童吗？ - 是的
- Hey, this is the Boy Wonder? - Yeah.
这位应该是他迷人的爱人吧
And his lovely lady. Yeah!
很高兴认识你 哥们
Hey, it's good to meet you, man.
我很激动你能加入这个团队
I'm excited you gonna join the crew.
厄 我想我…
Uh... I mean I...
你找到住的地方没？
You find a place to live yet?
我跟你说 你应该去住威尼斯公寓
I'm tellin' you, Venice is where is at...
- 我就住那儿 我可以带你去逛逛 - 谢谢
I live there, so I can show you around. - Thank you.
- 我得去下洗手间 - 好的
- I have to go to this little girls room. - Alright.
别 亲爱的 艾琳！
No... babe... Elaine!
她真的很辣 干的漂亮！
She is smokin', nice job dude. Excellent.
该走了！该走了！
- Way to go! - Way to go!
女孩们 你们好吗？
Whats going on ladies?
- 抱歉 - 这是怎么回事？
- Sorry. - What is that about?
- 上帝啊 - 好吧 听着
- Jeez us! - Okay, look.
好的 我也没必要瞒你了
Ok, its obviously out of the bag...
我觉得你应该搬到洛杉矶来
I'm thinking uh... You should move to LA.
我在这能干什么？我在老家都快活不下去了
What am I gonna do in here? I'm barely surviving back home.
我可以雇你
I can use you.
噢 我不需要你的施舍 明白？
Oh, I don't need your charity, alright?
好吧
Ok fine!
我需要你
I need you.
我对场景特效一无所知
I don't know anything about effects man.
- 真是扯淡 拜托 - 我不骗你
- That's bullshit, come on! - That's not bullshit.
你应该明白你很有天赋的 电脑只是一种工具罢了
You got the eye and you know it. Alright! The computer is just a tool.
我不清楚 反正我没想过要待在这
I don't know, I've never saw myself out here.
那你觉得你应该去哪？
Where do you see yourself?
难道你已经有了好的打算不想让我知道？
You got a fine A-B plan I do not know about?
这和钱没关系 好吗？
It is not about the money, okay?
一切都是为了钱的
It's always about the money.
艾琳怎么办？
What about Elaine?
我照顾不了所有事 你还是自己解决吧
I can't handle everything. You got to take care of that yourself.
特里 楼上有你的电话
Terry, there is a call for you upstairs.
好好想想吧
You think about it.
艾琳
Elaine.
好啦 别这样
Alright, come on.
我们只是过来玩的 怎么回事？
We suppose to be having fun, what's the problem?
别提了 好吧
Just forget it, alright!
听着
Look...
特里今天才把所有来加州的事情都告诉我
Terry sprung this whole California thing on me today, alright.
我之前并不知情
I had no idea...
太“晚”了
I'm "late"...
什么叫“太晚了”？
What do you mean you "late"?
我怀孕了！
"Late"!
噢 抱歉
Oh, sorry.
从什么时候开始的？
Since when?
我不知道
I don't know.
我不舒服好几个星期了 所以就做了个检测
I've been feeling sick all weeks, so I took a test and...
为什么不告诉我？
Why didn't you tell me?
我想过的
I wanted to...
相信我 我不想破坏你的行程
Believe me... I just I don't want to ruin your trip.
你怎么这么想
You thought.
该死的
Shit!
这就是你要说的吗？
Is that all you have to say?
那你要我怎么说？
What would you want me to say?
- 我觉得我还没准备好接受这件事 - 你没准备好 杰里德？
- I don't think I'm ready for this. - You not ready, Jarrod?
那我怎么办？
What about me?
不是的 嘿 你能不能…！
It's not... Hey will you kid...!
这不就是我们所期望的吗？
Isn't that what we've look forward to?
艾琳
Elaine...
等等 我看到了 看到了 瞧那个家伙
Wa... wa... wait... we got it... we got it take a look at that one.
就像我说的 冠军出来鸟！
We have a winner! That what I'm talking about!
不好意思 女士
Pardon me ma'am, but...
我们收到很多噪音扰民投诉
...we received a few noise complaints.
谁说的？
From who?
整座楼一半都是空的
The building is half empty.
我知道 但是其他住户需要休息
I understand that but, the other half is trying to sleep...
所以你不介意的话
...so if you don't mind ...just
好吧
Fine.
又发生了一件搞笑的事
Another one for the books... Oh yeah.
- 好吧 - 沙发是我的
Well, well, well. - I call the couch.
没事啦 这沙发很大的
Oh come on, there is plenty room for both of us.
我想一个人待这
I like more space.
噢 好吧 随你找什么借口
Wow, alright. Maybe can be excuses.
晚安
Good night.
第一天 凌晨4:27
来自火星的蜘蛛
地震了吗？
Earthquake?
或许只是微震罢了
Probably just a Tremor.
把灯关了吧
Turn off the lights.
雷
Ray.
你在干嘛？
What are you doing?
雷！
Ray!
待这别动
Stay here.
- 发生什么事了？ - 他消失了
- What wrong? - He is gone!
杰里德 不要去！杰里德 不要啊！
Jarrod, no! Jarrod, no!
- 发生什么事了？ - 特里 你快点来啊！
- What the hell is going on? - Terry, please, you got to hurry!
你想干嘛？哥们
What's got you man?
杰里德！
Jarrod!
这是怎么回事？
Please... What's happening?
杰里德！天哪！
Jarrod! Oh my God!
他怎么了？
What's wrong with him?
雷去哪呢？
Where is Ray?
- 雷呢？ - 不 别
- Where is Ray? - No, no, no, no...
他在哪？
Where is he?
- 他消失了！ - 什么意思？
- He is gone! - What do you mean he is gone?
他消失了
I mean he is gone.
- 他掉下去了？ - 不是
- Did he fall? - No!
- 还是他跳下去了？ - 我不知道 不知道
- Did he jump? - I don't know! I don't know!
振作点 振作点
Please, please...
他向外面的那道光走去
He went outside, to the light.
之后他就消失了 我不知道
And then, he just disappeared... I don't know.
特里 别走！
Terry, please!
杰里德 看着我
Jarrod, look at me.
你刚才看到了什么？看到了什么？
What did you see huh? What did you see?
发生了什么？
What happened?
杰里德 刚才到底怎么了？
Jarrod, what happened?
我不知道
I don't know.
我被拽着朝那束光走去
I was being pulled to...towards this light.
- 打开百叶窗！ - 不要！
- Open the blinds! - No!
- 给我打开百叶窗！ - 我不！
老天！
God!
那下面有东西
There is something down there.
什么？
What?
杰里德 你看下吧
Jarrod, check this out.
我看不到有什么东西啊
I don't see anything.
在那 有人在楼顶
There, people on the roof.
他们在干嘛？
What are they doing?
不知道
I don't know.
我们得去核实一下
We should check it out.
你根本不了解外面的情况
You don't know what's out there.
- 我还好 - 好的
- Everything Okay. - Alright.
我要报警
I'm calling the police.
- 我得去拍些照片 - 你不可以出去
- I'll get some pictures. - You can't go out there.
我不能让特里单独行动
I can't let Terry alone.
电话没人接
It just keep ringing.
需要带枪吗？
A gun?
有必要吗？
Really?
我去看下外面究竟发生什么事了
Just check the news and find out what the hell is going on.
特里！
Terry!
我们马上就回来！
We will be right back!
- 杰里德 - 看着我
- Jarrod. - Look at me.
我们走吧
Let's go.
早点回来
Hurry back.
楼梯在这边
The stairs are this way.
我靠
God dammit...
怎么回事？
What's going on?
我只是出来查看下情况
I'm going to check it out.
那你干嘛还带着枪？
What are you doing with a gun?
快回你的房间去 快点
Go back to your apartment. Go!
还有别出声
And keep it down.
你确定吗？
Are you sure about this?
自从凌晨4点后就没任何新闻了
There is been nothing news since 4 a.m.
丹尼斯 打开电视看下
Denise, check the TV.
出奇的安静
Its calm.
该死的 杰里德
Dammit, Jarrod.
你没说要我开着门啊？
You didn't tell me to hold it open.
我以为你会这样做
I tought it was common sense.
对不起
I'm sorry.
趴下
Get down.
现在怎么办？
What now?
去找个好的观测点
Let's get a better look.
你好 我是杰希 请留言
Hi. This is Jackie. Please leave a message.
妈 是我
Mom, its me.
发生了些事
Something happened uh...
快接我电话
Pick up.
快点…
Please, just...
收到留言马上打给我
...call me back as soon as you get this.
天哪！
Holy shit!
- 我看不清 - 是我想得那种情形吗？
- I can't see it. - Is that what I think it is?
上帝啊！
Oh my god!
- 快跑 - 那是什么？
- Just run. - What is it?
快跑！快点 跑啊！
Run! Just run! Go!
快点 打开它
Come on, push.
退后！退后！
Back off! Back off!
用力啊！
Come on!
用力！
艾琳 不要！
Elaine, no!
- 让开 让开！ - 好的
- Move, Move! - Okay.
亲爱的 你还好吧？
Baby, are you okay?
我现在感觉就像被火烧一样
I feel like I'm in fire now.
把那给我 快点给我！
Give me that, give it to me!
我保证马上就好了
It will stop immediately. I promise.
没事了
Its alright.
你也看过它
You look too.
怎么会这样？
How?
天哪！
Oh my god!
所有人
All those people.
它们要他们干嘛？
What do they want with them?
我可不想知道原因
I'm not looking to find out.
天哪 真是难以置信！
God, I can't believe this...
怎么会这样？
I mean how?
你一旦看着那道光
Once you look at the light...
它就会把你吸住
...it grabs hold.
- 就像… - 它控制了你
- It's like... - It controls you.
谁会拒绝去看如此美妙的东西呢？
I mean who wouldn't stare at something so beautiful?
某种程度上这的确很壮观
It's kind of brilliant actually.
我受够了
Enough with this shit.
我有个想法
I got an idea.
你去哪儿？
Where are you going?
- 去沃尔特那儿 - 为什么？
- Walt's. - What for?
别担心 一切在掌控之中
- Don't worry about it. - Everything is under control.
你没事吧？
Are you okay?
是的 不碍事
Yes. Its not matter.
让我看下
Let me see.
我说了我没事
I said its not...
- 好吧 - 我…
- Alright. - I uhh...
沃尔特
Walt?
呦！沃尔特
Yo. Walt?
沃尔特？
Walt?
你在吗？
Are you in here?
- 你在这干嘛？ - 躲起来
- What the hell are you doing? - Hiding.
我看见很多人飞到天上
I saw the people, in the sky.
还有天煞的飞船
With the god damn raptor.
走吧！
Come on!
我开车带你离开这里 我们走吧！
I take you in the car and get the hell out of here. Let's go!
我可不想出去
I'm not going out there.
趴下！趴下！
Get down! Get down!
别让狗叫！别让狗叫！
Shut the dog! Shut the dog!
不！
No!
沃尔特！
Walt!
你听到了吗？
Did you hear that?
发生什么事？快告诉我！
What's up? Talk to me!
乘上我的游艇 我们离开这
We get on my boat and get out at here.
到底怎么了？
What happened?
它们抓走了沃尔特
They took Walt.
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
有个怪物和我们看到的不一样 它能钻进楼房然后抓走他们
This one was different. It came in the building and just snatch 'em.
那我们得马上离开了！
Then we should just go!
等一下
Hold on a sec.
难道只有我看过这些照片吗？
Am I the only one who saw these photos?
现在外面到处都在发生这种事 它们无处不在
That's all happening right outside Right now! They are everywhere.
不 并不到处都是
No, they are not everywhere.
- 它们并没有在有水的地方出现 - 他说的没错
- They are not over the water. - He's right.
是的 但它们也没花多少时间就在屋顶发现了你们
Yeah, well it didn't take 'em very long to find you on the roof.
我们可以在两分钟内到达那儿
We can drive there in two minutes.
你根本不清楚它们有多厉害
You have no idea what their capable of.
我知道你很害怕 我们也是
I know you're scared... okay We're all scared...
但是我可不想坐以待毙…
But I'm not burying my head...
什么都不做等着事情好转
in the sand and open this cause away
- 我不是这个意思 - 嘿 冷静点 哥们
- I'm not saying that. - Hey, look. Just take it easy, man.
- 现在不是说冷静的时候 - 我明白
- There is no easy about this. - I understand that.
- 它们现在就在这座该死的楼里 - 特里？
They're in the fucking building. - Terry?
时间到了
It's the timer.
天哪…
Oh my god...
该死！
Shit!
快躲起来！快！快！快！
Hide! Go! Go! Go!
你真恶心！
You're disgusting!
你这是怎么了？
What the hell is the matter with you?
- 之后再说 - 好的 之后说
- We talk about that later. - Yeah, we will talk about that.
还打算待在这吗？
Still want to stay?
我不会接受你的决定的 它们是不会发现我们的
I don't want any of this, they don't see us or hear us
因此如果我们待在这不出声的话
so if we stay here and stay quiet...
那能维持多久？
For how long?
很明显 它们正在外面忙着抓人类
They're picking people out there. Plain and simple.
越早离开对我们越有利
The further we can out of this city, the better off we are.
他说的没错
He's right.
杰里德
Jarrod.
如果我们登上游艇 那我们就有活下去的希望了！
If we get to the boat we have a chance!
- 是的 可是如果我们没登上 - 我们必须登上！
- Yes, but if we don't... - We have to!
我们得试一试
We have to try.
拿上你的行李
Get your stuff.
带上水和食物
Get food and water.
行动吧
Let's do this.
走
Let's go.
一切正常 跟我来
Alright, come on.
听着 我一到那 游艇马上就开
Look, the sooner I get there, The sooner the boat ready to go.
特里
Terry...
- 嘿！ - 好的 我们走吧！
Hey! - Come on, let's go.
你想干嘛？
What are you doing?
开车去 我知道怎么走！
Driving, I know the way!
- 记得带上你的小三 - 康迪斯！
- Just take your slut. - Candice.
康迪斯！
Candice!
上车！
Get in the car!
特里 对不起！
Terry, I'm sorry.
- 快点 - 没看见我正在忙吗？
- Hurry up. - What do you think I'm doing?
嘿 停车
Hey, slow down.
不要
No.
停车
Stop.
你们需要帮忙吗？
You need any help?
- 不需要 我们能摆平 - 好的 但是或许…
- No, just go, we're fine. - Yeah, but maybe...
够了 闭嘴！我说了我们不需要
Enough, alright! I said we are fine.
特里 快逃！
Terry, get off!
特里！
Terry!
我抓住你了！
I got you!
杰里德！快回来！
Jarrod! Get your ass back at here now!
开车！快开车！
Drive! Drive now!
你们想做什么？
What are you doing?
快点！
Come on!
开门！
Open!
噢 该死的 给点力啊！
Oh shit! Come on!
- 快开门！ - 快点啊！
- Open! - Come on.
快开门你这鬼东西！
Open you piece of shit!
退后！退后！退后！快点！
Back off! Back off! Back off! Go!
不！我的天哪！
No! Oh my god!
天哪！快跑！
Oh my god! Go!
快！这边！
Go! This way!
康迪斯 快拿钥匙！快拿钥匙！
你们没事吧？
Are you alright?
我没事
Yeah I'm okay.
上帝啊！
Oh my god!
女士 我们得离开这
Miss, we got to go.
不 我们…
No, we...
他还活着！
He is alive!
科林！
Colin!
帮帮我！
Help me!
快走！快点！
Come on! Let's go!
走啊！
Go!
走后门
Make for the back door.
快跑！
Run!
跑！快跑！
Move! Move!
加把劲！
Come on!
别停下来！
Don't stop!
快开门！
Open the door!
让我来！
Get off me!
- 退后！ - 打开它！
Back off! Open it!
快点！
Come on!
楼顶是我能想到的最安全的地方
All the way to the top is the safest place that I can think of.
如果它们在那该怎么办？
What if they're there?
如果你喜欢待在这的话 那我也没办法！
And if you like being here with that, be my guest!
我们走吧！
Let's go.
快点！快点！快点！
Come on! Quickly! Quickly! Quickly!
我本应该去救他的！
I should have helped him.
嘿！过来帮忙！
Hey! Come help me with this.
这总比什么都没有好吧？
It's better than nothing, right?
是 随你怎么说吧
Yeah, if you say so.
你这是在干什么？
What are you doing huh?
谁都不想发生这种事情
Like it or not this is happening.
你得坚强点
You got to be strong.
你们还好吧？
Is everybody okay?
你受伤了吗？
Are you hurt?
- 没 - 我挺好的
No... I'm okay.
- 现在该怎么办？ - 待在这
- What now? - We stay here...
先观望 等人来救我们
We keep watch, and we pray that someone comes.
没错
He's right.
肯定有人会来的
Someone is gonna come.
这不会持续很久的
It isn't come out forever.
对吧？
Right?
宝贝 我们最好待在一起
Sweetie, it is best if we stay together.
我不要
I can't.
她在抽烟
The smoke...
这种情况下我只是抽烟这已经很好了
Giving this circumstances, I think smoke is more than reasonable.
康迪斯
Candice...
我怀孕了 明白吗？
I'm pregnant, alright?
而且我觉得要在这么大的压力之下…
And I just thought that...and with all the stress...
没事了
It's okay.
我都不敢告诉我妈
I never have the guts to tell my mom.
来吧 让这两个女孩休息一下 我们来保护
Come on boss. Let the girls get some sleep. You and I keep watching.
我们两个吗？
Both of us?
如果它们使用那道光的话 我们也好有个照应
If they're trying that light stuff, We got each other back.
我恨洛杉矶
I hate LA.
一晚上我都没见着个人
I haven't seen a soul all night.
或许最坏的事情已经结束了
Maybe the worse is over.
可能不是
Maybe not.
你觉得这些怪物是什么？
What do you think these things really are?
我不知道
I don't know.
这很重要吗？
Is that even matter?
这似乎只是一场噩梦
It's just doesn't seem real.
这是事实
Well it is real.
你最好清醒点
You better wake up.
你这话什么意思？
What's that suppose to mean?
这座城市已经没有生机了
This city hasn't a blink of life.
我们得勇敢地活下去
We need to survive.
像我们这样的幸存者没几个了
There is gonna be not many of us live.
看到什么了？
What do you see?
有人正在反击
Somebody is fighting back.
- 你要干什么？ - 我去看下外面发生了什么？
- What are you doing? - I want to see what's out there.
把它关掉！
Turn that off!
太显眼了！
It's too bright!
- 不！ - 我们不能这样冒险！
No! - We can't risk it!
我的天哪！
Oh my god.
第二天
你一晚都没睡吗？
Did you sleep at all?
越来越严重了吗？
Was it getting worst?
什么？
What?
你皮肤上的疤痕
The marks on your skin.
当我看着那束光时 我坚持不了10分钟
You know when I looked to the light, I couldn't stand for 10 minutes.
谁知道那些怪物对我们做了什么？
Who knows what it did to us.
还是在我们身上
To our bodies.
你还记得你第一次看到它的时候吗？
You remember the first moment when you saw it?
当它完全占据你的思想
When it completely took over.
会感觉…
It's kind of uh, use to feel...
充满力量
...down to the floor.
我仍然有这种感觉
And I still do.
为啥你不坐下呢 放松点
Why don't you take a seat, relax.
好吧 我开问
Alright, I'll bite.
你有什么想法吗？我知道你很想告诉我
What's your plan boss? Because I know you're dying to tell me.
不想说吗？
Nothing to say?
我们现在就在该死的码头边上
We are sitting on the marina, for Christ sake.
是的 我注意到了
Yes, I notice that.
而街对面就有几百条空船
And there are hundreds of boats right across the street.
这些我们都尝试过了
We've been through all this.
你还记得上次失败的教训吗？
Remind us how we've failed that last time.
我们这次悄悄地去
We go quietly this time.
然后在每条船上搜直到找到船钥匙？
And search every boat until we find the key?
如果可以的话
If we have to...
真是个好主意 杰里德
Great plan, Jarrod.
真难以相信 经过那么惨痛的经历后你还是坚持这种想法
I can't believe you even suggested that after what happened.
这不是我的错
It wasn't my fault.
当时我是多么强烈地乞求
I was frenetically begging...
可是你却不听
...but you wouldn't listen.
你觉得特里会听我的吗？
And you think Terry would've listened to me?
好吧
All right...
就算我们安全的离开了这里
Let say we make it out of the building.
穿过港口到了码头
Accros the marina, down the dock
就算找到了船 万事俱备 然后呢？
we even find a boat, and everything never mind...
- 然后我们就可以离开这个鬼地方 - 去哪？
- And then we get out the hell of here. - Where to?
沿着海岸去北卡罗来纳州？
Carolina, down the Coast?
- 去哪都比这好 - 你怎么知道
- Anywhere is better than here! - How do you know?
我们待在这！
We are here!
至少可以活下来！
We are alive!
那是什么？
What was that?
你看到什么了？
What do you see?
谢天谢地！
Hallelujah.
加油！加油啊！
Come on! Come on!
所有人都趴下！
Everybody get down!
艾琳？
Elaine?
成功了
It worked.
难以置信 一切结束了吗？
I can not believe it! Is it over?
成功了
It worked.
我看下好吗？
May I?
去吧
All this yours, boss.
你觉得他们会派更多的战斗机来吗？
You think there are more planes where they came from?
是的
Yes.
他们现在知道该做什么了
Now they know what to do.
他们马上就会来救我们的
They will be sending help at no time.
看到什么？
What?
那是什么？
What is it?
它们没被消灭
They're not dead.
他们现在被惹毛了！
They are just really... really pissed off.
有事发生了
Something is happening.
我们得把这些窗户遮起来
We have to cover these windows.
快过来帮我
Come help me with this.
回来！
Come back over here!
我去找些东西
I'll find something!
给
Here.
杰里德 你在干嘛？
Jarrod, what are you doing?
干你不想干的事！
Something you can't!
你究竟想怎么样？
What's this really about huh??
这些怪物冲我们而来
These things are coming for us.
你以为我不知道你身上那块东西么？
You think that I haven't notice that mess under your shirt.
好好待在这才是最好的选择！
We will stay here, and hold up, for good!
我同意
I agree.
我还以为我可以做决定呢
Well, I guest I decide everything.
这里既没水了 也没电
We have no water. No power.
是的 但是你睁大眼睛看下外面是什么情况
Yeah, but you saw what's out there.
我知道
Yeah.
我宁愿去争取一下
And I will rather make a run for it...
也不想待在这二十层的大楼里
...than stay in a 20 storey building.
被那些怪物和辐射包围
Between those things and the radiation
最终我们会死在这的
...we are done up here.
放开我！
Get off me!
- 你他妈的在想些什么？ - 我们得让他们知道我们在这儿
- What the hell are you thinking? - We have to let 'em know we're here.
- 你知道什么！ - 你之前说过我们等着被救援的
- To hell everything you know! - You've been saying to wait for help.
现在救援部队就在眼前了
The help is here!
那像救援飞机吗？
Does that look like a rescue chopper to you?
你还不明白吗？
Don't you get it?
我们正身处战争中！
We're at war!
他们要去哪？
Where are they going?
直升机等下还会来 我们必须离开这
Those choppers will coming back for them. We have to go.
跟我走！
Come on!
我们去楼顶 让他们带上我们
We'll go to the roof. Get them to pick us up.
如果他们不回来怎么办？刚才那些战斗机的下场你也看到了
What if they not come back? Look what happened to those planes.
- 直升机会比战斗机更好？ - 我们得抓住机会！
- Look all those helicopters? - We have to take a chance!
机会？
A chance?
他们刚刚用核弹毁了这座城市
They just nuked the city.
难道你还妄想和他们打招呼吗？
And you want to wave hello?
我警告你 马上给我退后！
Seriously You need to back off!
你得…
You have to...
该死的！
Oh shit!
你还是想那么站着吗？
You just gonna stand there?
剩下的窗帘掉下来后怎么办？
What happens when the rest of the blinds fall?
我们都没有足够的床单
We don't have enough bed sheets.
- 走吧！ - 你怎么这么确定？
- Come on! - How can you be so sure?
我们走吧！
Let's go!
你没权力做出任何决定了
You have no condition to decide anything.
而且谁知道你现在站哪边！
Who knows whose side you are.
我警告你
I'm warning you.
别动手！你们两个！
Stop it! Both of you!
看他的脸
Look at his face.
他病的不轻啊
He is sick.
- 别逼我出手！ - 噢 这不必你担心
- Do not make me hurt you! - Oh don't worry.
我不会离开我的家人的
I'm not leaving without my family.
没有人可以阻止我们的
And there is nothing that...you can do to stop us.
艾琳 你必须相信我
Elaine, you have to trust me.
是我
It's me.
我还是原来的我
I'm still... me.
我知道
I know.
我们得走了
We have to go.
他会把她害死的
He is gonna get her killed.
跟我来
Come on.
走吧
好的 我们走吧
Alright, let's go.
你看到他们了没？
Did you see them?
他们在那
They're right there.
- 救命啊！ - 别动！
- Help Us! - Don't move!
- 别开枪！ - 不 不 等等
- Don't shoot! - No, no, wait!
- 站在那别动！ - 我们需要帮助！
- Remain where you are! - We need help, please.
现在过去
Go there now.
不要啊！
No!
这里有两个幸存的市民 我们得把他们送走
We have two civilians, we got to way them out.
明白 我看到了 马上降落
I got it, we have visual on the two, get down right now.
不！
No!
快跑
Come on.
放开我！天哪！
Get it off me! God!
快跑！快跑啊！
Go! Go! Go!
那儿有脚手架
The scaffolding.
这是唯一下去的方法 快过去！
It's the only way down. Go, go!
快点啊！
Come on!
艾琳 快跑啊！
Elaine, run!
见上帝去吧 狗娘养的！
Vaya con dios, son of a bitch!
救命啊！
Help me!
救命！
救我啊！
Help me!
杰里德
Jarrod.
看着我
Look at me.
看着我啊 杰里德
Look at me, Jarrod.
起来 快点！
Get up, come on!
艾琳 求你了
Elaine, please.
快走啊！
You have to go.
我不能丢下你一个人走
I'm not going anywhere without you.
第三天
杰里德！
Jarrod!
不要！
No!
我的孩子啊！
My baby!
杰里德
Jarrod...
本片除特效费用外的实际成本为50万美金
包含特效费用后的总制作成本为1000万美金
本片的全球票房为6500万美金
本片制片公司称本片会拍续集
本片制片公司同时也是特效制作公司
曾为《终结者3》 《神奇四侠》系列 《X战警》系列
《300》 《阿凡达》 《2012》 《钢铁侠2》等电影
制作过特效
本片制片公司还是即将上映的《洛杉矶之战》
"Battle: LA"的特效制作公司 其制作成本为7000万美金
谢谢观赏
TLF中文字幕站：http://tlfsubs.eastgame.org/
微博地址：http://t.sina.com.cn/tlfsubs
博客地址：http://blog.sina.com.cn/tlfbest